Guide to the Jean Kilbourne Papers, 1918-2014 and undated RL.10982
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1970-2006 and undated; 9; 11 boxes
  - RL10982-VHS-0070. 2014-0217. Dreamworlds 2: Deisre, Sex, and Power in Music Video. TRT ~56:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0071. 2014-0217. Material Witness: Race, Identity and the Politics of Gangsta Rap. TRT 42:00. VHS. Original. 1995 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0072. 2014-0217. Toxic Sludge is Good For You: The Public Relations Industry Unspun. TRT 45:00. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0073. 2014-0217. Reviving Ophelia: Saving the Selves of Adolescent Girls. TRT 35:00. VHS. Original. 1998 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0074. 2014-0217. Speak Up: Improving the Lives of Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgendered Youth. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 2001 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0075. 2014-0217. Advertising and the End of the World. TRT 47:00. VHS. Original. 1998 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0076. 2014-0217. Gar Mahood Interview by Bill Cameron on CBS Evening News. VHS. Original. 1995 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0077. 2014-0217. Sexual Harassment: Building Awareness on Campus. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0078. 2014-0217. Sexual Harassment: Building Awareness on Campus. VHS. Original. 1995 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0079. 2014-0217. What a Girl Wants. TRT 32:35. VHS. Original. 2000 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0080. 2014-0217. A Tether of Romance: Byron de Prorok and the Tomb of Tin-Hinan. TRT 17:00. VHS. Original. 2001 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0081. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne at 1997 NACA National Convention Showcase. TRT 27:37. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0082. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne Lecture at Exeter Academy. TRT 76:00. VHS. Original. 1996 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0083. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne on Oprah. TRT 60:00. VHS. Original. 1989 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0084. 2014-0217. January Series- Can't Buy Me Love. For Jean Kilbourne. TRT 63:00. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0085. 2014-0217. On Television: The Violence Factor. TRT 60:00. VHS. Original. 1984 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0086. 2014-0217. New England Today. VHS. Original. 1985 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0087. 2014-0217. Woman to Woman. Miracle of Life. Alcoholism. TRT 5:06:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0088. 2014-0217. Marketing Misery Teleconference- University of Georgia. TRT 4:56:00. VHS. Original. 1989 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0089. 2014-0217. TV Ads in Seattle, Washington. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0090. 2014-0217. Anderson Cooper. On the Record With Bob Costas. Oprah. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0091. 2014-0217. Jean on the Today Show. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0092. 2014-0217. Studio 4: Show 403. Guests Ted Field and Jean Kilbourne. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0093. 2014-0217. No Title. VHS. Original. 1985 and 1986 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0094. 2014-0217. No Title. VHS. Original. 1986 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0095. 2014-0217. Donahue. TRT 60:00. Cronicle-Jean. TRT 30:00. Behind the Sell. TRT 60:00. Donahue. TRT 60:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0096. 2014-0217. Jean on 10 o'clock news. Jean on 5:30 news. Jean on Channel 5 news. VHS. Original. 1989 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0097. 2014-0217. Jean on Oprah. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0098. 2014-0217. 20/20. VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0099. 2014-0217. Our Times. VHS. Original. 1989 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0100. 2014-0217. Duxbury Dialogue #110 with Jean Kilbourne. VHS. Original. 1992 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0101. 2014-0217. Healthbeat One Hour Special. Final. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0102. 2014-0217. Jean on Early Show. Jean Files. NewsHour 43918. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0103. 2014-0217. Sex Files: EPS #3- Boob Tube'. VHS. Original. 2004 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0104. 2014-0217. Acohol Advertising: Should it be Banned? The Oprah Winfrey Show. Bad Copy. VHS. Original. 1989 (Box AV3)
  - RL10982-VHS-0105. 2014-0217. The Famine Within. TRT 90:00. License Copy. VHS. Original. 1992 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0106. 2014-0217. Buy Me That, Too. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0107. 2014-0217. Scanning Television: Videos for Media Literacy in Class, Video 3. The Global Citizen (part 1) and New and Converging Technologies (part 2). TRT 65:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0108. 2014-0217. Scanning Television: Videos for Media Literacy in Class, Video 3. Our Constructed Worlds: Media Environments. TRT 41:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0109. 2014-0217. Scanning Television: Videos for Media Literacy in Class, Video 2. Selling Images and Values. TRT 57:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0110. 2014-0217. Drink Sells the Dream. VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0111. 2014-0217. Making a Killing: Philip Morris, Kraft and Global Tobacco Addiction. TRT 29:00. VHS. Original. 2000 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0112. 2014-0217. The Culture Jammer's Video. TRT 12:00. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0113. 2014-0217. Buy Me That: A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising. TRT 28:00. VHS. Original. 1990 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0114. 2014-0217. Listen Up! New Voices, New Activists. Weekend Workshop Production Tape. TRT 11:00. VHS. Original. 2000 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0115. 2014-0217. Scanning Television: Videos for Media Literacy in Class, Videa 1. Seeing Ourselves: Media and Representation. TRT 1:28:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0116. 2014-0217. Madeline's Rescue. TRT 25:00. VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0117. 2014-0217. Chronicle- Cued up. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0118. 2014-0217. Chronicle- Little Girls. Geraldo at Large. Today. VHS. Original. 2006 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0119. 2014-0217. Prime Time Live: Jean Kilbourne. Woman's Health. VHS. Original. 1994 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0120. 2014-0217. Pure Oxygen, Show #217. B&C Blocks- Cigarette Advertising. VHS. Original. 2000 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0121. 2014-0217. Greater Boston. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0122. 2014-0217. Untitled. VHS. Original. 1987 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0123. 2014-0217. A Woman's Health. TRT 58:00. VHS. Original. 1994 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0124. 2014-0217. 20/20, Jean Kilbourne. Also something from from 1994. VHS. Original. 1991-1994 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0125. 2014-0217. Untitled. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0126. 2014-0217. WNT- Dave Ads. VHS. Original. 2005 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0127. 2014-0217. Prime Time Live: Sexy Ads. VHS. Original. 1994 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0128. 2014-0217. To the Contrary: Sexism in Advertising. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0129. 2014-0217. Deadly Persuasion: Contact 4. VHS. Original. 2000 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0130. 2014-0217. The Edge- Fox News. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0131. 2014-0217. Clearing the Air. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 1996 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0132. 2014-0217. Clearing the Air. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 1996 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0133. 2014-0217. 1997 Counter Cilos Awards. CNN Story on Counter-Cilo. Mark Miller on CNN. TV Ontario Story on Counter-Cilos. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0134. 2014-0217. Limited: The Body Test. TRT 47:58. VHS. Original. 1988 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0135. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne on the Alan Gregg Show. TRT 27:25. VHS. Original. 2000 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0136. 2014-0217. Houston Effler Herstek Favat. Department of Public Health. Master Reel #2. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0137. 2014-0217. Video Games 2003: The State of the Art- The Lion & Lamb Project. TRT 10:40. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0138. 2014-0217. Houston Effler Herstek Favat. DPH Master Reel. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV4)
  - RL10982-VHS-0139. 2014-0217. Keep it Zipped. :30 and :60 versions. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0140. 2014-0217. Game Over: Gender, Race and Violence in Video Games. TRT 41:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0141. 2014-0217. Playing Unfair: The Media Image of the Female Athlete. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0142. 2014-0217. Recovering Bodies: Overcoming Eating Disorders. TRT 34:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0143. 2014-0217. What Kids Want to Know About Sex and Growing Up. TRT 60:00. VHS. Original. 1992 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0144. 2014-0217. SmokeScreeners Program Video- An educational program to take the glamour out of smoking in the movies. TRT 14:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0145. 2014-0217. Clearing the Air. Nick News. VHS. Original. 1996 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0146. 2014-0217. In the Mix #424- Self-Image: The Fantasy, The Reality. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0147. 2014-0217. In the Mix. Media Literacy: TV- What You Don't See! TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0148. 2014-0217. Animation and Truth. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0149. 2014-0217. Being Obese. TRT 24:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0150. 2014-0217. Rock and Porn Connection. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0151. 2014-0217. Mass. DPH Tobacco Control. Commercials. Master Reel. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0152. 2014-0217. Marketing Booze to Teens: Alcopops Media Advocacy. VHS. Original. 2001 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0153. 2014-0217. Sex in Advetising: Users and Affects. TRT 34:00. VHS. Original. 2001 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0154. 2014-0217. All Men are Sons. TRT 55:00. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0155. 2014-0217. Stuart Hall: Representation and the Media. TRT 55:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0156. 2014-0217. Stuart Hall: Race, the Floating Signifier. TRT 60:00. VHS. Original. 1996 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0157. 2014-0217. Stuat Hall: Race, the Floating Signifier. TRT 60:00. VHS. Original. 1996 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0158. 2014-0217. Twenty Commercial Spots. TRT 13:00. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0159. 2014-0217. Media Sharp: Analyzing Tobacco and Alcohol Messages. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0160. 2014-0217. Sex, Lies and Profits: A Critical Look at the Advertising Practices of the Alcoholic Beverage Industry. TRT 17:00. VHS. Original. 1994 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0161. 2014-0217. Refuse to be Used. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0162. 2014-0217. Mass. Dept. of Public Health; Antismoking spots 2000. VHS. Original. 2000 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0163. 2014-0217. Peter Elbow on Writing. TRT 43:00. VHS. Original. 1995 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0164. 2014-0217. Framing an Execution: The Media and Mumia Abu Jamal. TRT 70:00. VHS. Original. 2001 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0165. 2014-0217. Livin' on the Net (Volume 2): Virtual Communities and the World Wide Web. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 1996 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0166. 2014-0217. Livin' on the Net (Volume 1): E-mail, Newsgroups, FAQ's and Virtual Communities. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 1996 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0167. 2014-0217. Behind the Scenes: Hollywood Goes Hypercommercial. TRT 37:00. VHS. Original. 2000 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0168. 2014-0217. Mental Engineering (show #204). TRT 26:40. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0169. 2014-0217. The Ad and the Id: Sex, Death and Subliminal Advertising. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0170. 2014-0217. Mental Engineering (show #204): Bars and Tone. TRT 26:40. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0171. 2014-0217. Mental Engineering (show #210): Bars and Tone. TRT 26:40. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0172. 2014-0217. Rebelling Against Tobacco Ads. TRT 58:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0173. 2014-0217. I'm Possible: Cam Neely Pilot. TRT 22:30. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0174. 2014-0217. Reel Girls. TRT 19:00. VHS. Original. 2001 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0175. 2014-0217. Sex, Death and Advertising. TRT 70:00. VHS. Original. 1991 (Box AV5)
  - RL10982-VHS-0176. 2014-0217. Frontline: The Merchants of Cool. TRT 60:00. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0177. 2014-0217. Children's Television: A Day in the Life of Your Child!. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0178. 2014-0217. Don't be a TV: Television Victim. TRT 18:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0179. 2014-0217. Medienkoffer: Das Frauenbild in den Medien. Set 1. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0180. 2014-0217. Medienkoffer: Das Frauenbild in den Medien. Set 2. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0181. 2014-0217. Warning: The Media May Be Hazardous to Your Health. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0182. 2014-0217. Minnesota Department of Health. Rich, Oasis, Kirby, Butts, Contest and Animals. TRT 180:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0183. 2014-0217. Teen Sexuality in a Culture of Confusion. TRT 40:00. VHS. Original. 1998 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0184. 2014-0217. Alcohol's Seduction of Teens: Alcohol's Assault on Children. TRT 48:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0185. 2014-0217. More Fun, Less Stuff: The Challenges and Rewards of a New American Dream. TRT 30:00. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0186. 2014-0217. Mental Engineering (show #212): Bars and Tone. TRT 26:40. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0187. 2014-0217. CH. 7 News. Gender Gap and Plastic Surgery with Jean Kilbourne. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0188. 2014-0217. House mag with Jean Kilbourne, Jim Peterson. 20/20 Best Kept Secret. Under the Influence. The People Inside me. Every Parents Nightmare. Young and Innocent. Wilson Key on Letterman. Last Word on Mass Murders. X-rated Video Games. Look at us on Media Violence. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0189. 2014-0217. Off the Straight and Narrow: Lesbians, Gays, Bisexuals and Television. TRT 63:00. VHS. Original. 1998 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0190. 2014-0217. The Myth of the Liberal Media: The Propaganda Model of News. TRT 60:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0191. 2014-0217. Liar Liar Tights on Fire. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0192. 2014-0217. Edward Said on Orientalism. TRT 40:00. VHS. Original. 1998 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0193. 2014-0217. National Geographic Millenium Special. Adventures in Time. TRT 87:27. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0194. 2014-0217. Healing and the Mind: Volume #1 The Mystery of Chi and #2 The Mind Body Connection. TRT 112:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0195. 2014-0217. Bill Clinton on Arsenio Hall. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0196. 2014-0217. War Zone: A Film About Sex, Power and What Happens When Men Threaten a Woman's Right to Walk Undisturbed on the Streets. TRT 45:00. VHS. Original. 1998 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0197. 2014-0217. The Electronic Sotryteller: Television and the Cultivation of Values. TRT 32:00. VHS. Original. 1997 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0198. 2014-0217. Stuart Hall: Representation and the Media. TRT 55:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0199. 2014-0217. Katz Womens Career Summit opening. TRT 5:00. VHS. Original. Undated. (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0200. 2014-0217. Searching for Angela Shelton Break the Silence. TRT 94:00. VHS. Original. 2004 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0201. 2014-0217. Defending Our Lives. TRT 41:00. VHS. Original. 1993 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0202. 2014-0217. Independent Media: In a Time of War. VHS. Original. 2003 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0203. 2014-0217. Breaking Our Silence: Gloucester Men Speak out Against Domestic Abuse. TRT 11:00. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0204. 2014-0217. Picture Perfect. TRT 40:00. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0205. 2014-0217. Body Talk 1: Teens Talk About Their Bodies, Eating disorders and Activism. TRT 28:00. VHS. Original. 1999 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0206. 2014-0217. Body Talk 2: It's a New Language. TRT 20:00. VHS. Original. 2002 (Box AV6)
  - RL10982-VHS-0207. 2014-0217. I.B.: Survival Story. VHS. Original. 2004 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0001. 2014-0217. Last Word: MLM #47. TRT 60:00. 3/4-inch. Original. 1982 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0002. 2014-0217. The Joel Spivak Show: Women Adu. 3/4-inch. Original. 1979 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0003. 2014-0217. Mills-Oteri Dub. Jean Kilbourne. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0004. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly (Rev). 3/4-inch. Original. Undated. (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0005. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. 3/4-inch. Original. Undated. (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0006. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. 3/4-inch. Original. Undated. (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0007. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly (rev). 3/4-inch. Original. Undated. (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0008. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. 3/4-inch. Original. Undated. (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0009. 2014-0217. WNAC-TV Boston Weekday: Teens and Alcohol. 3/4-inch. Original. 1981 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0010. 2014-0217. Up to the Minute- CBS-TV. TRT 30:00. 3/4-inch. Original. 1981 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0011. 2014-0217. New England Today: Alcohol and Advertising. Interview with Jean Kilbourne. 3/4-inch. Original. 1981 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0012. 2014-0217. Point of View with Judy Jarvis. 3/4-inch. Original. 1981 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0013. 2014-0217. The Naked Truth. Presentation in Dallas. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0014. 2014-0217. Evening Magazine with Jean Kilbourne. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0015. 2014-0217. New England Today: Alcohol Advertising. 3/4-inch. Original. 1985 (Box AV7)
  - RL10982-3/4-0016. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly. TRT 29:00. 3/4-inch. Original. 1979 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0017. 2014-0217. New England Today with Jean Kilbourne. WLV1-TV Boston. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0018. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne: Women in Advertising. WGBY-TV Springfield, Mass. TRT 9:55. 3/4-inch. Original. Undated. (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0019. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne on the Today Show. 3/4-inch. Original. 1974 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0020. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne interview with Garland Waller on rape #2. 3/4-inch. Original. 1984 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0021. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne interview with Garland Waller on rape #1. 3/4-inch. Original. 1984 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0022. 2014-0217. Women in Advertising Mack Mills reporting. TRT 9:55. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0023. 2014-0217. The Changing Images of Females and Males in TV Commercials. 3/4-inch. Original. 1981 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0024. 2014-0217. Evening Magazine with Jean Kilbourne. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0025. 2014-0217. The Joe Oteri Show. WLV1-TV Boston. 3/4-inch. Original. 1979 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-3/4-0026. 2014-0217. Jean Kilbourne interviewed on At Noon. WNAC-TV Boston. 3/4-inch. Original. 1979 (Box AV8)
  - RL10982-V32-0001. 2014-0217. The Joe Oteri Show. Under the Influence. Boston. 3/4-inch. Original. 1979-1980 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-V32-0002. 2014-0217. Joel Show #2. 3/4-inch. Original. 1979 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-V32-0003. 2014-0217. Joel Show #1. 3/4-inch. Original. 1979 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-V32-0004. 2014-0217. Unlabeled. 3/4-inch. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-V32-0005. 2014-0217. Jean on Television. WGB4-TV. Springfield, Mass. Mark Mills. Evening Magazine. WB2. Boston. New England Today. Boston. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 and undated (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-V32-0006. 2014-0217. Cannot Read Entire Title. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-V31-0001. 2014-0217. Night Scene-WNAC. J. Kilbourne- S.O.H.-WCVB. 3/4-inch. Original. 1978 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVCam-0001. 2014-0217. Still Killing Us Softly. TRT 31:29. digital-8. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVCam-0002. 2014-0217. Killing Us Softly. TRT 29:12. digital-8. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0001. 2014-0217. Prime for Life: Utah. dvd. Original. 2001 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0002. 2014-0217. Prime for Life: Utah. dvd. Original. 2001 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0003. 2014-0217. Prime for Life: Under Twenty One. dvd. Original. 2001 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0004. 2014-0217. Jean Archive #6: Duxbury Dialogue. To the Contrary- Maryland Public Television. Prime Time Live- National. A Woman's Health- KCTS Seattle. Clearing the Air- Nick News, National. Counter-Clio Awards. Chronicle- Boston. Greater Boston. The Edge with Paula Zahn. Fox News, National. dvd. Original. 1992-1999 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0005. 2014-0217. Jean Archive DVD #1. dvd. Original. 1978-1979 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0006. 2014-0217. Claudia on Good Morning America. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0007. 2014-0217. Jean Archive #7. dvd. Original. 1999-2000 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0008. 2014-0217. Jean Archive #5. dvd. Original. 1986-1991 and undated (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0009. 2014-0217. Jean Archive DVD #2. dvd. Original. 1979-1981 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0010. 2014-0217. Jean Archive DVD #4. dvd. Original. 1982-1985 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0011. 2014-0217. Jean Archive DVD #3. dvd. Original. 1981-1982 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0012. 2014-0217. The Sex Files. dvd. Original. 2004 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0013. 2014-0217. Jean Nationals #1. dvd. Original. 1979-1994 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0014. 2014-0217. Jean Nationals #2. dvd. Original. 1996-2006 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0015. 2014-0217. Counter-Clios. dvd. Original. 1997 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0016. 2014-0217. Garland Waller Interview. dvd. Original. 1984 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0017. 2014-0217. Jean Archive #8. dvd. Original. 2000 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0018. 2014-0217. Jean Archive #9. dvd. Original. 2003-2006 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0019. 2014-2017. Marketing Misery Teleconference. 2 Disks. dvd. Original. 1989 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0020. 2014-2017. Woman to Woman. 2 Disks. dvd. Original. 1984 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0021. 2014-2017. New England Today. dvd. Original. 1985 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0022. 2014-2017. On Television: The Violence Factor. dvd. Original. 1984 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0023. 2014-2017. January Series: Can't Buy My Love. dvd. Original. 2003 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0024. 2014-2017. Opra. 2 Disks. dvd. Original. 1989 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0025. 2014-2017. Lecture at Exeter. dvd. Original. 1996 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0026. 2014-2017. NACA Showcase. dvd. Original. 1997 (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0027. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #1. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0028. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #2. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0029. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #3. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0030. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #4. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0031. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #5. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0032. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #6. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0033. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #7. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0034. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #8. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0035. 2014-2017. Jean Archive #9. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0036. 2014-2017. Jean Nationals #1. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)
  - RL10982-DVD-0037. 2014-2017. Jean Nationals #2. dvd. Original. Undated. (Box AV9)